{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf755ed47bf2e548c927"},"product_asin":"B07F8H9PGS","QAs":[{"question":"What is its MRP?","answer":"Go to product website","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Subhas Chandra Mondal","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product contain bleach? Is it 100% bleach free?","answer":"Yeah","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Subhas Chandra Mondal","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long is the expiry?","answer":"No expiry","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Subhas Chandra Mondal","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use surf excel quick wash in my Samsung top load washing machine","answer":"Definitely you can","votes":"0","username":"ANSUMAN S.","date":"2021-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"One kg package is available","answer":"Yep","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Subhas Chandra Mondal","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"For how much order delivery charges will be waived off ??","answer":"Above Ra499 free delivery","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Subhas Chandra Mondal","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is measure cup provided","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Subhas Chandra Mondal","date":"2019-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is measure cup provided","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"shantanu debnath","date":"2019-10-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the delivery charges ?","answer":"No ,I happy for Amazon thanks for free delivery","votes":"0","username":"Sayyed mukhim","date":"2019-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the delivery charges ?","answer":"Delivery Charges is free","votes":"0","username":"VR2","date":"2019-05-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf765ed47bf2e548c932"},"product_asin":"B07F9ZRRJG","QAs":[{"question":"What is the Mrp of this product?","answer":"1325","votes":"0","username":"Prity gupta","date":"2022-09-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many packets of detergent in the box??","answer":"One Pack of 1 KG, instead of Two packs of 1 KG each.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"I think in this box they gave spoon to to measure dosage but There is no spoon inside","answer":"Normally, we receive one plastic measure spoon in each one kg packet.","votes":"0","username":"Radhakrishna","date":"2022-02-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I subscribe it it again?","answer":"üëç good quality","votes":"0","username":"Rehana A Nadaf","date":"2021-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use for onida top load machine?","answer":"Yes, this product can be used with any Top Load washing machine from ang brand.","votes":"0","username":"Rana","date":"2021-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date and manufacturing date of this product?","answer":"As on today we r selling Manufacturing date is 12/20","votes":"0","username":"Mahila Udan Kendra","date":"2021-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this detergent for LG semi automatic washing machine","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-02-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Used for front door l g machine fully automatic","answer":"this is for Top Load can u for fully automatic machine","votes":"0","username":"Mahila Udan Kendra","date":"2021-01-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Refund me","answer":"why refund","votes":"0","username":"Sankar dey","date":"2021-02-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"This item surf excel 4+20kg is applicable for return of refund too plz do it","answer":"No I think it's not","votes":"0","username":"ekta singh","date":"2021-02-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf775ed47bf2e548c93f"},"product_asin":"B08D8NNRDT","QAs":[{"question":"Is it pack of 3.?","answer":"Yes , it‚Äôs pack of 3","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Singh","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used for top load washing machine?","answer":"Undoubtedly. You can go for and for a fantastic result .","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Singh","date":"2022-02-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 1 pack or 3 packs of 3kg?","answer":"Price  very very high....","votes":"0","username":"P.M.SHAHUL HAMEED","date":"2022-02-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf775ed47bf2e548c943"},"product_asin":"B07PZWWJKK","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have a scoop in the 4kg pack?","answer":"Yes, it does come with a scoop.","votes":"0","username":"Belmond Chongtham","date":"2022-08-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Validity period to return item  su‚Å∏9rf excel powder 3+1 kg  front load","answer":"10 days","votes":"0","username":"Raja","date":"2021-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Shall i use front loading machine powder. In top loading washing machine","answer":"Yes it will work in both type of machines","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh","date":"2021-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between top load and front load powders","answer":"According to my experience there's better results from top load surf powder","votes":"0","username":"Raja","date":"2021-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's best before date","answer":"Best before date means the expiry date is given ya months see on the box .if u keep properly it doesn't get spoil  u can use after expiry date.","votes":"0","username":"Natalina Fernandes","date":"2021-09-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Surge excel 3kg + 1kg is free but u didn‚Äôt give","answer":"In one box 4 packets comes. It is 3+1free.i ordered many times i got the correct one.","votes":"0","username":"Natalina Fernandes","date":"2021-09-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product date","answer":"05/21","votes":"0","username":"Raja","date":"2021-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"‡§â‡§§‡•ç‡§™‡§æ‡§¶‡§® ‡§§‡§ø‡§•‡§ø ‡§ï‡•ç‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§π‡•à","answer":"2002","votes":"0","username":"manoj jain","date":"2021-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"I ordered for 4+2kg surf excel front load. But got only 4kg without any label how could i trust you?","answer":"Please call on Amazon customer care number they will help you.","votes":"0","username":"Natalina Fernandes","date":"2021-09-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"I ordered for 4√ó2kg surf excel front load. But got only 4kg without any label how could i trust you?","answer":"It's simple... Just return the product with photo/video proof and call customer care  of AMAZON.","votes":"0","username":"Raja","date":"2021-10-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf785ed47bf2e548c94e"},"product_asin":"B07F9X4S5T","QAs":[{"question":"6 kg in one packet or 1kg each in 6 packet","answer":"1kg in 6 packets","votes":"0","username":"Anjali Shah","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"804421 not delivered","answer":"I got this product as per the delivery shedule mentioned","votes":"0","username":"Kishu l asrani","date":"2021-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is bleach free or not","answer":"I found after using the colour of the garment is clean and shiny.  Hence it is supposed to be Bleech free. If bleach is added th colour of garment becomes dull.","votes":"0","username":"VVR","date":"2021-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have you changed the fragrance. I am feeling that I got a duplicate stuff.","answer":"Fragrance is sane and you can feel it after washing and drying.  However if one needs more fragrance add COMFORT ‚Äò conditioner.","votes":"0","username":"VVR","date":"2021-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How it possible tat surf excel matic front load 4 kg plus 2 kg free , if cost is 1098","answer":"It costs Rs  183/- per kg.  Which is reasonable.  Supplier should think of giving 4+3 Kgs. So that sales will boosts up.","votes":"0","username":"VVR","date":"2021-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"If that product was damage,what shall I do..","answer":"Ask for free replacement.  Damage depends upon the quality of the clothing.","votes":"0","username":"VVR","date":"2021-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What shall i do if i received old  product","answer":"Return and ask for compensation.","votes":"0","username":"VVR","date":"2021-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to send the link","answer":"Best","votes":"0","username":"Mritrunjay K.","date":"2020-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"May I use it in LG front load washing machine?","answer":"Thank you for choosing our product. Yes you can use Surf Excel Matic Front Load Detergent Powder for LG front load washing machines.","votes":"0","username":"Hindustan Unilever Limited.","date":"2020-12-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date?","answer":"Don't know i brought for my mom she is in India","votes":"0","username":"Ramandeep kaur","date":"2020-07-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf785ed47bf2e548c959"},"product_asin":"B0963XJG72","QAs":[{"question":"For all type of washing we can use ?","answer":"Front load","votes":"0","username":"Paul","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Surf Excel liquid and Shot both need to use for washing or only shot is enough?","answer":"Depends upon cloth, how dirty they are. If you are washing your daily attire, better use only shot, if clothes are toodnirty and have some stains, use mixed one","votes":"0","username":"Sanjay","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What do u mean by 1 load? I have 7kg load capacity washing machine.. Does 1 pod will be enough?","answer":"One for,up to 5 kg","votes":"0","username":"Arun Bishnoi","date":"2022-10-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many smart short contains ?","answer":"17 pieces","votes":"0","username":"Sumaiyah Tazyeen","date":"2022-10-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it works in sami automatic machine","answer":"Yes u can use it.  The same way earlier u used use power detergent then liquid detergent now in shots it will consist of detergent fabric conditioner and fragrance and stain remover all in one","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i wash my tatoo from this?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shilpa","date":"2022-10-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product contains fabric conditioner also","answer":"This does not contain fabric conditioner, for that use EZEE liquid detergent with fabric conditioner instead of Surf, however if u wash clothes with Surf liquid u don't separately need any conditioner coz the clothes come out fresh","votes":"0","username":"Gupta Gupta","date":"2022-02-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"We have use washing powder along with shot","answer":"The shots have to be used alone, please do kot put ant other detergent along with the shot.","votes":"0","username":"Carmencita","date":"2022-01-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use for woolen cloth  ?","answer":"Yes, it can be used for any type of clothes. It's safe.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-01-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i add 1 shot in front load mission directly can i add cloths r after filling water i sud add cloths","answer":"If ur machine opens the door without draining water, u can add load, else don't waste ur Surf shot and close the door only when u have completed loading","votes":"0","username":"Gupta Gupta","date":"2022-01-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf785ed47bf2e548c964"},"product_asin":"B07PXND4T6","QAs":[{"question":"Can i use this in front load machine ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Binay Kumar Jain","date":"2022-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Selected item. How to order?","answer":"Excellent 4√ó1kg box","votes":"0","username":"Khaja mohiddin","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are there different 1kg pack in box or complete 4kg pack","answer":"Yes 1kg√ó4 pieces","votes":"0","username":"Khaja mohiddin","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Date off manifested","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Binay Kumar Jain","date":"2022-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I change the order qty to 1?","answer":"Don't change your pre Order you can be cancel  your order than submit New order.","votes":"0","username":"Vinod Singh","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why there aint no mfd on this product?","answer":"I think expiry date is essential for medicine and food products.","votes":"0","username":"Anil.S","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Picture says it is front load. but the description says it is top load. have told Amazon customer service executive yesterday about it. but no use.","answer":"You please read description, it's written for top load, it's for top load washing machines, don't see picture., I am using it for top load.","votes":"0","username":"Jagdish Kalra","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"On description it's written top load and on picture its written front load (purple colour). Which is correct","answer":"Read description only, don't see picture.","votes":"0","username":"Jagdish Kalra","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it front load or top load washing powder??","answer":"Top load washing powder","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-03-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it front load or top load powder as description is different then the image","answer":"Description is rightly written.","votes":"0","username":"Jagdish Kalra","date":"2022-03-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7a5ed47bf2e548c975"},"product_asin":"B07SGS93PJ","QAs":[{"question":"What about the expiry date of the item","answer":"Thank you for choosing our product. The expiry date of Surf Excel Matic Top Load Detergent Powder is best before 24 months from the date of packaging.","votes":"0","username":"Hindustan Unilever Limited.","date":"2020-07-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7a5ed47bf2e548c977"},"product_asin":"B00U2DUE1A","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be used in lg front load automatic washing machine","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ramki","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Qjat is the expiry dates of this product if i buy now","answer":"Please check with the seller in the product description.","votes":"0","username":"Ramki","date":"2021-11-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is surf excel quick wash can be used in washing machines?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"m.i_Ansari","date":"2021-11-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used for washing by hands?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"RAVI SHANKAR","date":"2021-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Surf excel quick wash white powder","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anon","date":"2020-11-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"This surf excel has bleach in it, whereas lots of clothes come with clear instructions to not use bleach. Is it going to damage the clothes?","answer":"less powder wont hurt the clothes.","votes":"0","username":"Anon","date":"2020-11-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which clothes we have to use for surfexcel quick wash","answer":"I use this for all our clothes since years. Haven‚Äôt noticed any issue so far.","votes":"0","username":"Ramki","date":"2020-09-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Anything free","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"pankaj","date":"2019-10-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have white powder?","answer":"Good quality packing safe","votes":"0","username":"Sai Kiran Sarma","date":"2019-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is that pack of 2 for 2kg","answer":"No...It's a 2 kg pack","votes":"0","username":"Rahul sharma","date":"2019-06-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7a5ed47bf2e548c983"},"product_asin":"B00TS89BSW","QAs":[{"question":"Is it a mild detergent?","answer":"Vgood nice and üòÉüòÉüòÉüòÉ","votes":"0","username":"Mary","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Marketing price 120 kg","answer":"It is worth for the price","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dispatched in 1 to 2 months means?","answer":"Best","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its front loading detergent powder","answer":"Normal detergent","votes":"0","username":"abinash sahoo","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"There isn't anything mentioned in the package. This being an item that one uses practically every day ,I haven't seen any deterioration in the product","votes":"0","username":"Roychi","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats the expiry date of this product?","answer":"There is no expiry date on this product","votes":"0","username":"Roychi","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date kya hai","answer":"03/2022","votes":"0","username":"Jayanti Chaurasia","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use top load machine ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"abinash sahoo","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it use for front load washing machine","answer":"I believe it could","votes":"0","username":"Roychi","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the color of this powder?","answer":"Light blue","votes":"0","username":"Jain","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7a5ed47bf2e548c98e"},"product_asin":"B079GXSVWD","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date of this product?","answer":"The product was under expiry date","votes":"0","username":"MD ZAFAR","date":"2022-08-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"This pack 6 kg or 5kg","answer":"6kg","votes":"0","username":"Komal gaur","date":"2022-01-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats is difference easy wash or quick wash","answer":"Dear CustomerPlease ask to the brand (Customer Care Number on the back side of the Product) they may answer you better in this regard.Stay Home Stay Safe.see less","votes":"0","username":"M2R TECHNOMATIONS LLP","date":"2022-01-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"When expire?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"sanjay mahto","date":"2021-11-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used in front loading washing machine?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amarjit Kumar","date":"2021-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this is one pack ?","answer":"No. It's 3 kgs. 2 packs.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used in fully automatic top load machine","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"BHATT VIVEK","date":"2020-02-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have free delivery for prime members??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"BHATT VIVEK","date":"2020-02-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used in frontloading machine","answer":"yes ir=t can be used","votes":"0","username":"Ganesh Subramanium","date":"2019-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have free delivery for prime members??","answer":"Do order on amazon prime","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7b5ed47bf2e548c99a"},"product_asin":"B01ITJ6642","QAs":[{"question":"What is the manufacturing date of this surf excel item?","answer":"I must have used many, many such packets purchased from different local shops and also from amazon. I do not recollect which particular pack you must be referring to. Mfg date is always printed on the pack.","votes":"0","username":"Kartik Tripathi","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I wants the bulk quantity for business  is this availble facility for","answer":"Yes available with Amazon‡•§ Business ‡•§","votes":"0","username":"Arizic online","date":"2021-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"I don't know exactly but i know  manufacturing date of the detergent  that was 18/01/2020 . üëç","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj kumar","date":"2020-03-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"expire date","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"mohamed ilyas","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expire date","answer":"Well it was well within the expiry date. I don't have the packet as we already used it. It was packed in month of June.","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh","date":"2019-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of the product","answer":"Beautiful","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"May I know the expiry date of this product?","answer":"If any validity of said item, please advise.","votes":"0","username":"Prem","date":"2019-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to buy some products from amazon but my pin code is not available at amazone .please add our pin code","answer":"761118","votes":"0","username":"Ramananda patro","date":"2019-02-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"I had orderfor 1 of 3 kgs surf excel buy 2 quantityis sent w can i return one packet","answer":"1","votes":"0","username":"mohamed ilyas","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is manufacturing date and expiry date ?","answer":"Manufaturing date is a date of Product packed for Sell and Expiry date is when the product is not efficient or not Useful for Use","votes":"0","username":"Jagdish sonawane","date":"2018-06-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7c5ed47bf2e548c9a5"},"product_asin":"B07RK4NNM3","QAs":[{"question":"Is the container a pet jar or packet?","answer":"Packet","votes":"0","username":"M.V","date":"2022-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"His expiri date?","answer":"Expiring in September 2023","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7c5ed47bf2e548c9a8"},"product_asin":"B00U2DUC9O","QAs":[{"question":"Cashpayment on delivery","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Thomas J.","date":"2020-10-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 3+1kg","answer":"No only 1 kg","votes":"0","username":"Vishal Yadav","date":"2019-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Am  using  this for front load any problem","answer":"Nothing Any Problem","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2017-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"i have 7.2kg fully automatic top load.how many quautity i need for normal and strong wash on 6 to 8 clothes do i need to add vanish with this?if yes","answer":"5","votes":"0","username":"9910404360","date":"2017-01-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why my higher price at Amazon not getting posted?","answer":"Because this product directly purchased from the company","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2017-02-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"1kg Amazon price is 207 and in shop it is 185.Where is saving using Amazon?","answer":"Being foolish at  Amazon..","votes":"-1","username":"Avik Aman","date":"2017-03-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the mrp of this surf?","answer":"215","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2016-09-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is 1kg top load washing powder mrp cost","answer":"180","votes":"0","username":"mohit badhwar","date":"2017-02-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Front Load washing powder be used in top load machine?","answer":"Yes, you can.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2016-04-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7c5ed47bf2e548c9b2"},"product_asin":"B079QKXP84","QAs":[{"question":"1 kg tide ka price","answer":"Price always mentioned in every product while selecting the product in Amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Green bazar","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any difference between this tide and tide natural ( yellow pack ) ?","answer":"Yes there is difference of smell and tide plus is superior than tide natural.","votes":"0","username":"Shiv Pandey","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya delivery charges alag se Hain","answer":"Pin code pe depend krta h,amazon prime pe depend krta h,offers pe depend krta hai","votes":"0","username":"RAVI TIWARI","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"can it be used in fully automatic washing machines?","answer":"I am sure it can be","votes":"0","username":"RAVI TIWARI","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"I am purchasing in bulk..but delivery charges are 77 per item..why so?","answer":"Depends on seller...its his wish if he wants to take delivery charge","votes":"0","username":"RAVI TIWARI","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Big pack is available or not","answer":"available","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2021-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"8 kg tide surf?","answer":"only  2 kg available","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2021-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Offer free delivery but shipping charge added in 'tide detergent'?","answer":"Could be possible","votes":"0","username":"RAVI TIWARI","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want 5 kg packet which has a free bucket","answer":"There will be a search option in amazon..try that once","votes":"0","username":"RAVI TIWARI","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why you dont upload mrp, expiry, mfg pictures of product????","answer":"Sellers don't do it because they don't want you to know the actual mrp of product...you can check it in nearby store and if you feel its on offer,then buy","votes":"0","username":"RAVI TIWARI","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7d5ed47bf2e548c9bd"},"product_asin":"B00NOZ3ZOQ","QAs":[{"question":"Is it safe for top load washing machines ?","answer":"Absolutely it is safe","votes":"0","username":"Anonymous","date":"2021-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it chlorine free detergent,Or not.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shyam k.","date":"2019-11-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free delivery","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shyam k.","date":"2019-11-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why did you charge Rs. 80 for delivery.Its your policy you only charged your delivery charges when product cost below 500.","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"VIKRAM PRATAP SINGH","date":"2019-10-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is extra delivery charge?","answer":"No, it is purchased within a pantry bucket size and hence no delivery charges added","votes":"0","username":"Navin Kumar","date":"2019-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is extra delivery charge?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Navin Kumar","date":"2019-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"Yes, it's so half-full and original","votes":"0","username":"Sanjay","date":"2019-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing and expiry date","answer":"As per use","votes":"0","username":"Ananda","date":"2019-04-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7e5ed47bf2e548c9c6"},"product_asin":"B07ZQDFG9R","QAs":[{"question":"Why this product isn't going in the cart?","answer":"Might be out of stock or unavailable.","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use automatic washing machine?","answer":"Yes sure with full confidence you can use for a good result and you will get shining clothes","votes":"0","username":"shahin","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mrp how much with offers","answer":"Dont buy this product.","votes":"0","username":"Placeholder","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"can it be used in fully automatic top  load machine ?","answer":"Dont buy this product.","votes":"0","username":"Placeholder","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing  date is mentioned in the packet or not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"imtiyaj","date":"2022-02-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this front load washing machine","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"ABDUL HAFIZ","date":"2022-01-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"May i know how this is a deal when i am getting the same product for Rs 790(tide 7+3kgfree","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"ABDUL HAFIZ","date":"2022-01-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many kg inside that","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"ABDUL HAFIZ","date":"2022-01-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why so costly.. local shop giving tide rose jasmine 2 kg 190 rs... made mistake to buy from Amazon fresh","answer":"Tide Jasmine Rose's MRP has changed","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"why you raised price so much lat i buyed it at 722 now it is 878?","answer":"Good itam ok","votes":"0","username":"ABDUL HAFIZ","date":"2022-01-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7e5ed47bf2e548c9d3"},"product_asin":"B079QJMVPX","QAs":[{"question":"is this woshing soda  insirted","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Roshan","date":"2021-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use in front load washing machine","answer":"Instructions given in tide packet how to use, please follow the company rules as given","votes":"0","username":"ORANGE MEN","date":"2020-07-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7e5ed47bf2e548c9d6"},"product_asin":"B079QKYMTY","QAs":[{"question":"How much i use it or expiry date of product tide 8 kg  detergent powder","answer":"Good product","votes":"0","username":"Vasim malek","date":"2022-10-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain 8 individual packets?","answer":"NO, you will only get 8 Kg Detergent in one packing","votes":"0","username":"Jitender Malik","date":"2022-10-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain 1kg packs packs of 8??","answer":"Nice, at discounted price","votes":"0","username":"Omprakash Khetan","date":"2022-10-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used for fully automatic washing machine","answer":"Yes, I'm using too..","votes":"0","username":"A. Talukdar","date":"2022-10-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for top loading automatic washing machine","answer":"Yes, I'm using too.. Getting positive good results.","votes":"0","username":"A. Talukdar","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date as for now","answer":"Nice product at reasonable price","votes":"0","username":"Omprakash Khetan","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pese to pure 8 kgs ke le rhe ho?","answer":"Dont buy this product.","votes":"0","username":"Placeholder","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this single packet? or is packaging in single 1 kg packets?","answer":"Dont buy this product.","votes":"0","username":"Placeholder","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please took on cash on delivery","answer":"Dont buy this product.","votes":"0","username":"Placeholder","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the MRP of this product","answer":"Rs 779","votes":"0","username":"yogeswari Jeyakumar","date":"2022-02-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf7f5ed47bf2e548c9e1"},"product_asin":"B00WUCSDI2","QAs":[{"question":"Total weight of the package ???","answer":"4Kg","votes":"0","username":"zayan faizan","date":"2017-02-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is in this pack one kg free","answer":"No. I feel I paid for the entire 5 KG Pack","votes":"0","username":"Krupakar J.","date":"2016-11-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf805ed47bf2e548c9e5"},"product_asin":"B079QBSYSX","QAs":[{"question":"Is it total 10 kg or 8 kg ? Please confirm","answer":"8 kg","votes":"0","username":"Lonappan","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Actually packet is 8kg or 6kg.?","answer":"8kg","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Kumar‚Ä¶","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manfacture and expiry date is not mention. How ca n we purchase","answer":"Seven hundred four only","votes":"0","username":"Sujit Kumar Mishra","date":"2021-12-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is MRP?","answer":"704","votes":"0","username":"Sujit Kumar Mishra","date":"2021-12-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is d soap powder product supplied wholly one pocket or 1kg each*8?","answer":"Whole one packet","votes":"0","username":"Ankit Anand","date":"2021-12-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for automatic machine","answer":"8kg single packing","votes":"0","username":"subhash dhukia","date":"2021-12-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Use in front lode whasing machine....","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ankit Anand","date":"2021-12-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitable for front load fully automatic washing machine","answer":"good","votes":"0","username":"Tsewang D.","date":"2021-10-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"The same product is available with big bazar @rs. 590. Why amazon is so costly","answer":"Amazon is brdt","votes":"0","username":"Tsewang D.","date":"2021-10-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use on converse shoes","answer":"Amazon is best","votes":"0","username":"Tsewang D.","date":"2021-10-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf815ed47bf2e548c9f1"},"product_asin":"B08HNN86T4","QAs":[{"question":"Can i use this powder for bosch front load washing machine?","answer":"Yes... It's highly recommend","votes":"0","username":"Haider a tangoo","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this detergent washing powder to wash clothes with hand?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"S mohakud","date":"2021-12-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this powder for Ifb fully automatic 3dwash","answer":"It's works fine.","votes":"0","username":"ADITYA","date":"2021-11-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it matic detergent?","answer":"Hi..","votes":"0","username":"Alka","date":"2021-11-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"the picture show 1scoop for front and 3scoop for top why","answer":"Top load actually uses more detergent compared to front, i feel fron load gets a better was as well...","votes":"0","username":"Haider a tangoo","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Tide double power/ extra power better than Tide ultra?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SUDHARMAN","date":"2021-12-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many grams of detergent is used per wash in top load machine?","answer":"Can't answer how many grams but... Use from half a scoop to full scoop depending on your machine weight","votes":"0","username":"Haider a tangoo","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it high efficiency Detergent? If yes, why do you say that?","answer":"Yes.... It cleans my clothes well and I also have a clean washing machine by the end of the wash.... which is very important.... I've been using the same washing machine for 8 years and I've used many detergents tide is one of the best.","votes":"0","username":"Haider a tangoo","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to make the payment","answer":"U can make a payment using card ya COD.see there are many options","votes":"0","username":"Natalina Fernandes","date":"2021-11-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"it is available for 10kgPack?","answer":"No at present it is come byeb","votes":"0","username":"Natalina Fernandes","date":"2021-11-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf825ed47bf2e548c9fc"},"product_asin":"B085SFKVVH","QAs":[{"question":"Can we use this for fully automatic machine also?","answer":"Yes. Can be used","votes":"0","username":"Somnath Sinha Mahapatra","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the mrp in this product","answer":"420","votes":"0","username":"Somnath Sinha Mahapatra","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can use in front load washing machine??","answer":"If you want to you can but when i was using this for top load it's giving best results.","votes":"0","username":"sourabh m.","date":"2021-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's enable to top loaded","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vandy","date":"2020-12-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between tide ultra and tide plus?","answer":"The difference is ultra and plus. (Tide is common) ü§£","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"product received today is found in damaged condition. what am I supposed to do?","answer":"You can just return it.","votes":"0","username":"Aman Khan","date":"2020-08-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the mrp of this product?","answer":"600","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Singh","date":"2019-09-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf825ed47bf2e548ca04"},"product_asin":"B079QKMX9D","QAs":[{"question":"Mrp of 4kg","answer":"490 rs","votes":"0","username":"Jyothi Ambekar","date":"2020-11-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiery date ?","answer":"All ok go for it","votes":"0","username":"Swapnendu Dutta","date":"2017-02-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf835ed47bf2e548ca07"},"product_asin":"B07RNRQMJQ","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be used for hand wash?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-03-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"None","votes":"0","username":"Navin Talwar","date":"2020-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it in top load washing machine?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Navin Talwar","date":"2020-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is liquid","answer":"It a powder meant for top loading machine.","votes":"0","username":"SR Ramanathan","date":"2019-12-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you use with Front Loading machine?","answer":"It is specified for top loading machines.  I have usd for front loading machines also with good rersults.","votes":"1","username":"SR Ramanathan","date":"2019-12-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it for front load","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Navin Talwar","date":"2020-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it in front load washing machine?","answer":"Surely","votes":"0","username":"Rahul P","date":"2019-08-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use this for front-load machines ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Navin Talwar","date":"2020-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used for Front loading washing machines?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Navin Talwar","date":"2020-03-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it suitable for front load machines as well?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Navin Talwar","date":"2020-03-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf835ed47bf2e548ca14"},"product_asin":"B01CIC3V26","QAs":[{"question":"Is this powder useful for bosch washing machine?","answer":"Yes. It's for all brand.","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2019-10-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this powder useful for Bosch washing machine?","answer":"Yes. It's for all brand.","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2019-10-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this powder useful for bosch washing machine?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free Shipping","answer":"Depends on seller","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it not costly from d mart mega store","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"indian style kitchen design","date":"2018-06-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf845ed47bf2e548ca23"},"product_asin":"B07BDN3CCG","QAs":[{"question":"Is this 1kg or 800grams ?","answer":"1 kg","votes":"0","username":"jindal76","date":"2022-09-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tide liqidd available  ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2020-12-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be a delivery charge free item?","answer":"you have to pay for delivery !","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2020-11-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date??","answer":"April 2022.","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2020-11-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it original product","answer":"Yes Sir !","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2020-08-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf845ed47bf2e548ca2a"},"product_asin":"B07N6NP5K2","QAs":[{"question":"What is the manufacturing date?","answer":"05/09/2022","votes":"0","username":"mdenterprise¬Æ","date":"2022-09-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"‡§µ‡§ø‡§µ‡§∞‡§£ ‡§¶‡•á‡§ñ‡§®‡•á ‡§∏‡•á 7‡§ó‡•ç‡§∞‡§æ‡§Æ ‡§µ‡§ú‡§® ‡§≤‡§ø‡§ñ‡§ï‡§∞ ‡§≠‡•á‡§ú‡§æ ‡§ó‡§Ø‡§æ ‡§π‡•à ‡§ú‡§¨‡§ï‡§ø ‡§µ‡§ú‡§º‡§® 7‡§ï‡§ø‡§≤‡•ã‡§ó‡•ç‡§∞‡§æ‡§Æ ‡§∞‡§ñ‡§®‡§æ ‡§ö‡§æ‡§π‡§ø‡§è","answer":"Weight of item it self speaks with its volume.","votes":"0","username":"Ashok Tripathi","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for washingmachine","answer":"you can use in both","votes":"0","username":"Dr. A.","date":"2021-12-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there is any fees for delivery","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Dr. A.","date":"2021-12-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wish to buy but don't wish to pay delivery charges","answer":"try adding some other necessary item from the list of \"free delivery above ‚Çπ499\" to avoid delivery charges","votes":"0","username":"Sameera Khan","date":"2021-10-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"7 gram or 7 kg gram","answer":"7 kilograms","votes":"0","username":"Sadhana Hansda","date":"2021-10-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it white powder or blue?","answer":"White","votes":"0","username":"Harish Tiwari","date":"2021-10-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a original Rin powder????","answer":"Yes! It is a genuine product","votes":"0","username":"Sameera Khan","date":"2021-10-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which type of packaging provided by you?? As shown in picture or a transparent polybag??","answer":"The product comes packed in original Rin Detergent Packet as shown in the picture above & then they pack it in a cardboard box","votes":"0","username":"Sameera Khan","date":"2021-10-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing date","answer":"Everytime they send a recently manufactured product, & if its already expired you may choose to return or exchange it without any hassle","votes":"0","username":"Sameera Khan","date":"2021-10-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf845ed47bf2e548ca36"},"product_asin":"B01G4UJZK0","QAs":[{"question":"Can this be used for front load washing machines","answer":"Every type of washing machine has different types of detergent wash, and front load machines are recommended for 'mix the detergent (Rin detergent) to machine detergent'.","votes":"0","username":"Yash K.","date":"2021-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"4 kg or 7 kg?","answer":"The best surf i have used till date, you can just go for it.","votes":"0","username":"Lungnila r.","date":"2021-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Other seller's are selling at 330 and you are selling this at 250 ,Is this genune Product or not?","answer":"Original","votes":"0","username":"Nithi Enterprise","date":"2020-10-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya ye all tips cothes k liy h...imean color cloth","answer":"All clothes used","votes":"0","username":"Muni","date":"2020-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ye all tips cloths k liy sahi h","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RFGVRTGHTY","date":"2020-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"May i know the expiry date of 7 kg rin detergent powder?","answer":"Every pack has different date.. U can chk the dt after receive the packt","votes":"0","username":"Payal","date":"2020-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it make in India product?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"R.K","date":"2020-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this is suitable for semi automatic washing machine?","answer":"Yes..I have a LG 6.5 ltr Semi automatic machine..and i have been using Rin Refresh for the last 7 months to wash my daily use clothes in the machine..Works fine..","votes":"0","username":"Lakshmi","date":"2020-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rin 7kg detergent powder.pls","answer":"Yes i am entrusted","votes":"0","username":"R.K","date":"2020-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has for free home delivery","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Payal","date":"2020-07-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf855ed47bf2e548ca41"},"product_asin":"B00U2DU5BE","QAs":[{"question":"Rin soap","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"mdenterprise¬Æ","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rinsoap 4 It comes in pack of 4 - 250 gms each","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep Biramane","date":"2022-08-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"The price increased on amazon from 64 to 104? in last 6 months. Why is amazon inflating the price like this","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep Biramane","date":"2022-08-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rin soap 4","answer":"‡§∞‡§ø‡§Ç‡§® ‡§∏‡•ã‡§™ 4 ‡§ï‡§æ ‡§π‡•Ä ‡§™‡•à‡§ï‡•á‡§ü ‡§π‡•à","votes":"0","username":"CHANDER Dua","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rin soap 4 hu","answer":"yes - 4 nos of 250 gms each","votes":"0","username":"Krishnan Srinivasan","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rin soap 6","answer":"Please check with amazon","votes":"0","username":"Krishnan Srinivasan","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 4x250gm?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"VASUDEV COMMODITY","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the procedure for place order?","answer":"you can order on amazon","votes":"0","username":"Krishnan Srinivasan","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rin soap 10 250 2500","answer":"please check with amazon","votes":"0","username":"Krishnan Srinivasan","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rin doap 10 soap  1 peku","answer":"Please check with amazon","votes":"0","username":"Krishnan Srinivasan","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf855ed47bf2e548ca4c"},"product_asin":"B07ZNQNBZN","QAs":[{"question":"This is use for front load top machine","answer":"Top load","votes":"0","username":"Malathi","date":"2020-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mrp is Rs.99 but here Rs.199/- Why","answer":"I got it for 99/_ only","votes":"0","username":"Malathi","date":"2020-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf865ed47bf2e548ca50"},"product_asin":"B01NALS5VE","QAs":[{"question":"Wat is the best before date for this product","answer":"Dhulai krey aachey sey","votes":"0","username":"Promila","date":"2021-10-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want a 2 kg replacement of top loading arielmatic with a front loading arielmatic detergent powder","answer":"I trust on it","votes":"0","username":"Promila","date":"2021-10-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it produce foam while washing","answer":"No  such foam is there","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I see the same 2kg front load with less price, what is the difference between these two?","answer":"frond load vs toap load. front load is little bit expensive","votes":"0","username":"Sanjog Agrawal","date":"2019-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exp is 20th feb, 2019 but today is March 14. How you are selling expired products","answer":"Can't check the date. Mostly new dated.","votes":"0","username":"ABDUL","date":"2019-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between top load and front load matic washing powder.","answer":"Normally front load washing machine consumes lesser water for washing and rinse. So it required washing powder with high efficiency and low foam. This difference will be there in top load and front load washing machine.","votes":"0","username":"Pandian","date":"2019-02-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"what if clothes soaked in normal rin powder put for rince in front load washing machine????","answer":"No issues as such. But it is better if you use front load recommended powder.","votes":"0","username":"Suraj Datkar","date":"2019-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date of this product?","answer":"The received product manufactured date is Jan 2018.","votes":"0","username":"Ajith V S","date":"2018-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date","answer":"2019","votes":"0","username":"MMARTINDIA","date":"2018-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many packets does it contains  of detergent?","answer":"2 packets of 1 Kg each .","votes":"0","username":"COIMBATORE MANOJ","date":"2018-02-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf875ed47bf2e548ca5b"},"product_asin":"B0937TN8Y2","QAs":[{"question":"When it's expires ?","answer":"Look at the bottom of the bottle. You alone can find it.","votes":"0","username":"Niru","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this for hand wash","answer":"No only for clothes","votes":"0","username":"Evelyn Kumar","date":"2022-10-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"PKD DDMMYYYY","answer":"Check your bottle","votes":"0","username":"Niru","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ariel liquid vs surf excel liquid for front load which is a better option","answer":"Ariel liquid","votes":"0","username":"sk ayesha","date":"2022-08-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Amazon payments?","answer":"Ok","votes":"0","username":"Sunil kumar","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why costumers review Duplicate?","answer":"It may happen but Amozon completely responsible for such thing. Amazon only looks for their share not inpects the product. Therefore, many duplicate products, used product, broken or damage products also delivered to customers. It happened to me so I left purchasing from Amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Mehtab","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expury date?","answer":"Seller/Amazon will never say this after purchasing only you can be sure about this.","votes":"0","username":"Mehtab","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"I ordered it but its not delivered yet. Its been 3 more days than expected date.","answer":"Some times Amazon seller team cancells order by their own discrepency without any prior notice to customer. This may happed to you.","votes":"0","username":"Mehtab","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much ML liquid we need to use for 1 bucket daily clothes in washing machine?","answer":"60ml.","votes":"0","username":"G Suresh Dhas","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why amazon is not mentioning the MRP of this product?","answer":"This is a secrect of Amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Mehtab","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf885ed47bf2e548ca68"},"product_asin":"B071ZYNV95","QAs":[{"question":"350 for 6 kg ?","answer":"Don't know exactly, whenever I tried to buy it was never available at my pincode, I tired with many other pincodes, God knows where it is available?","votes":"0","username":"Anika Rana","date":"2020-01-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference in 4+2 kg arial top loading costing rs. 824  instead of rs. 350.00","answer":"Difference is only of quantity","votes":"0","username":"Anika Rana","date":"2019-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 6 kg pack in 350 rupees","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Kushwaha","date":"2019-11-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it original?cover packing doesn't look the same...","answer":"Yes It's a Originally One. Also i have Full trust on Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Kushwaha","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this original ariel?","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"Gautham","date":"2019-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"why I cannot order it??is there any limit","answer":"No door delivery","votes":"0","username":"Jeno","date":"2019-10-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the cost of delivery charge?","answer":"No delivery charge","votes":"0","username":"Jeno","date":"2019-10-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference in 4+2 kg arial top loading costing rs. 824  instead of rs. 350.00","answer":"In offer","votes":"0","username":"Jeno","date":"2019-10-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What amount to paid for 6 kg carton ariel matic","answer":"759","votes":"0","username":"suchi","date":"2019-10-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it 6 kg pack?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Aruna","date":"2019-10-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf895ed47bf2e548ca79"},"product_asin":"B078BCFQ7P","QAs":[{"question":"Does it comes with scoop?","answer":"No it doesn't contain any scoop","votes":"0","username":"Unknown","date":"2021-09-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Used for only white clothes??","answer":"You can used it for all types of clothes","votes":"0","username":"Unknown","date":"2021-09-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf895ed47bf2e548ca7e"},"product_asin":"B07BHHCG3M","QAs":[{"question":"Will it be 3X 1 kg packets??","answer":"Yes,3 number 1 kg packets.","votes":"0","username":"santosh","date":"2021-02-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with 500ml free ariel liquid as available in dmart?","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"Santa","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry. Date ?","answer":"Two years","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka","date":"2020-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can front load powder can be used for top load because by mistake i have ordeted","answer":"nothing special.. It is like daily washing powder..","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka","date":"2020-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its not delivered yet","answer":"Lack of consumer","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka","date":"2020-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered 3 kg but 1kg is missing. How can this happen with cloudtail seller? How they ship the item without checking?","answer":"Return the product","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka","date":"2020-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use it for normally washing cloth by hand.","answer":"Of course yes. But this is a bit expensive for that. There are cheaper options available. This is designed for the front load machine (to wash with less water and to enhance easy rotation as it produces less lather) it can be used for any washing Like any other detergent powder. Go ahead. Have a happy washing.","votes":"0","username":"Anto","date":"2019-10-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"In my order they gift shipment means what","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ashok","date":"2019-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it safe to use matic for bosch front load 8 kg","answer":"Yes, it is safe for all front load machine","votes":"0","username":"Harpreet Singh","date":"2019-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date","answer":"Manufacturing date 20/04/2019","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Krishnadas","date":"2019-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8a5ed47bf2e548ca8d"},"product_asin":"B01MRZZMYD","QAs":[{"question":"What do you mean by Front Load ?","answer":"This is specifically designed for using in front door washing machines.","votes":"0","username":"K. S.","date":"2022-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where i cancelled my order","answer":"Sure","votes":"0","username":"K. S.","date":"2022-02-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"I washed my pants with black dyed pants together accidentally, as a result I got my brown pants stain with some black marks. Is it going to effective?","answer":"Its actually depends on the quality of your cloth not the detergent","votes":"0","username":"Yash Prajapati","date":"2021-11-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"does 1kg top load powder come with a spoon inside?","answer":"Yes but the item is generally less expensive at Big Bazar","votes":"0","username":"‡§â‡§ß‡§Æ ‡§µ‡§ø‡§¶‡•á‡§∂‡•Ä","date":"2020-09-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this for samsung","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sajid khan","date":"2017-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use this Bosch front load washing machine?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nishant Nirmale","date":"2017-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use it in any washing machine ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"devesh","date":"2017-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is difference between ffront and top load and only front load ?","answer":"Front load is for front door washing machine and top load is for top opening washing machine","votes":"0","username":"Kanak Kartik","date":"2017-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"can it be used for hand wash","answer":"Yeah why not... But don't do","votes":"0","username":"Pk Pour Vous","date":"2017-03-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8a5ed47bf2e548ca98"},"product_asin":"B07BHH7JNL","QAs":[{"question":"Q: is 500g pack 200g free outside or inside.?","answer":"Inside","votes":"0","username":"Vinay Kr. Singhi","date":"2020-03-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8a5ed47bf2e548ca9a"},"product_asin":"B07RH199GJ","QAs":[{"question":"Whosing machine powder","answer":"Yes, it's for Semi Automatic Washing Machine Only","votes":"0","username":"VPSingh","date":"2022-10-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product can we use in fully automatic washing machine or not","answer":"Yes, Ariel Complete Washing Powder is okay to use in semi-automatic washing machines. However, if you have a fully automatic washing machine, it's better to use a laundry detergent that was specifically developed for that type, like Ariel Matic.","votes":"0","username":"SHREE BALAJI KIRANA STORE","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether it can be used top loading fully automatic","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Toqeer","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to buy it","answer":"Bilkul","votes":"0","username":"Toqeer","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"This pack come with total 6 kg","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Toqeer","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Date of Expired","answer":"Expiry","votes":"0","username":"Padmanabh Kulkarni","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Value pack mean","answer":"Expiry date usually relates to food items. This is soap. You can use this for a long time say year or two.","votes":"0","username":"Padmanabh Kulkarni","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of this pack?","answer":"Expiry date is for food items. This is soap","votes":"0","username":"Padmanabh Kulkarni","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mere pin code par cash delivery nhi ho pa raha hai","answer":"Online kardo","votes":"0","username":"Toqeer","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Total 4+2=6 kg???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PG","date":"2022-02-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8b5ed47bf2e548caa6"},"product_asin":"B08WBPD1L4","QAs":[{"question":"Please send me manufacturing date above pocket","answer":"Look on the packet","votes":"0","username":"VENKAT","date":"2022-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain any kind of a bleach or chlorine?","answer":"i dont know abt that. n i dont think it contains bleach or chlorine, we have been using it for years. its safe..has a good fragrance.","votes":"0","username":"sharfu.t","date":"2021-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it original product? There is no red ring in the middle of green rings","answer":"Come on man, I don't think somebody will make duplicate for detergents! (I don't know what you are asking, but may b the company changed the design or may b the picture displayed is an old one ). Also, if the seller is 'Cloudtail India', just buy with confidence... And if not that seller, check seller rating and if they are having good ratings, you should be fine!see less","votes":"0","username":"Kishore","date":"2020-09-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the fragrance","answer":"No fragrance.  Normal only","votes":"0","username":"Vinoth","date":"2020-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be used to Ariel matic powder in whirlpool washing machines","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Dhurwey","date":"2020-01-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date?","answer":"No expiry date","votes":"0","username":"Sekar","date":"2019-10-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why seller sent the wrong product, i lost my cashback offer and also time of 3 days","answer":"NOT WRONG PRODUCT BUT EXPIRY W.P.","votes":"0","username":"Md Abdus Sobur","date":"2019-11-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I wash colour clothes also from this.","answer":"Surely u can wash your colour clothes provided they are washed separately.","votes":"0","username":"Nikunj N.Chopdekar","date":"2019-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the product returnable","answer":"Yes it is returnable","votes":"0","username":"fahad basuleman","date":"2019-11-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this a china based company","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-08-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8c5ed47bf2e548cab3"},"product_asin":"B0794QPXTL","QAs":[{"question":"Cost? Awailable?","answer":"Cost is 1699","votes":"0","username":"FAMILY WEBTORE","date":"2018-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8d5ed47bf2e548cabb"},"product_asin":"B0BD235MBP","QAs":[{"question":"Kindly provide manufacturing date or Expiry date","answer":"Exellent product","votes":"0","username":"Ashikumar","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this for hand washing cloths","answer":"Exellent product","votes":"0","username":"Ashikumar","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why price in the packet is 370 only and the price listed on Amazon is 420. Also mrp is hided in the images","answer":"Refill pack is 375","votes":"0","username":"khaled","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is major difference in Front load n Top load detergent","answer":"The main difference between the top loader and front loader detergent is the suds or lather formula in the detergent. Since a front loading washing machine uses less water, it requires a high efficiency (HE) low suds formula detergent. The low suds formula of the HE detergents produces less lather and removes all the dirt and soap residue with less water.see less","votes":"0","username":"Rohit Kumar","date":"2022-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Howmuch quantity of liquid required for one pair of clothes?","answer":"10ml","votes":"0","username":"Ashikumar","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"The same product available on Flipkart @ Rs.400.00, why your price is too high ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ashikumar","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can I buy ariel front load liquid","answer":"You can buy online order Amazon, Flipkart etc. Site","votes":"0","username":"MD MOKARRAM HUSSAIN","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"We have paid 179 for prime membership then why we we r being charged for delivery charges","answer":"Might be the seller is charging, few items amazon will charge on delivery","votes":"0","username":"khaled","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many washes can we get in this 2litre pack if we use one measure of the bottle lid","answer":"45 times if use one cap per trip","votes":"0","username":"khaled","date":"2022-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much quantity should i use in 6.5kg fully automatic washing machine with half full tub?","answer":"Usually instructions are given on the pack , please follow that","votes":"0","username":"Indrajit","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8e5ed47bf2e548cad0"},"product_asin":"B01N4GLE1I","QAs":[{"question":"Not mentioned expire date?","answer":"Ariel powder is best if used 24 months from the date of manufacture; however instead of mentioning the date of manufacture, date when packed is mentioned. Ariel should modify suitably for clarity since date of manufacture and date of packing need not be same. Issue be taken up with P & G.","votes":"0","username":"RAJAN GOPALKRISHNAN","date":"2022-02-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Your rates Arial matick two kg rates are two high compare to rates at flipcartfor above product is twwo high","answer":"No you pay for 4 kg, but you get six kgs","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can It use For Samsung","answer":"For all washinh machines irrespective of its brand","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with plastic container?","answer":"No. Two pack inside with scoop only.","votes":"0","username":"ABDUL","date":"2019-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"This cannot be used for semi automatic washing machine? which is best for semi automatic top load machines?","answer":"Samsung","votes":"0","username":"chandan jha","date":"2019-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between front load & top load powder.why 2 different powder for same compny machine","answer":"Teka","votes":"0","username":"Ganta lachireddy","date":"2019-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use top load 6.5 KG ifb washing machine?????","answer":"Yah! You can use in any washing machine. But for best result use in front load washing machines.","votes":"0","username":"Vicky","date":"2018-10-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much delivery cost?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ashok","date":"2019-08-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why Delivery charge this iteam","answer":"because we also pay delivery charges on amazon","votes":"0","username":"indian style kitchen design","date":"2018-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"can I use it for semiautomatic washing machine?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"Melancia Rato","date":"2020-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8e5ed47bf2e548cadb"},"product_asin":"B071QXZQ9L","QAs":[{"question":"I want purchce today. When its expire date","answer":"Whenever I have bought the Ariel Powder the expiry date was approx. 6 to 10 months from Manufacturing date. So if you use it on daily basis the 6Kg shall get consumed within that time.","votes":"0","username":"Bhavin Patel","date":"2022-09-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this for top load washing machine. please suggest. since top load is out of stock in amazon","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ranjeet kumar","date":"2022-09-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its already expired?","answer":"No when I got the powder it was not expired. I have been buying since long time.","votes":"0","username":"Bhavin Patel","date":"2022-08-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the manufacturing date & expiry date","answer":"Mine packet manufacturing date was March 2022 and it is valid till 1 year.","votes":"0","username":"Bhavin Patel","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to order a Singal item in amezon fresh","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ranjeet kumar","date":"2022-09-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is mrp? and how would i order this","answer":"MRP of Ariel powder is much on higher side around 1500 so if you get Deal for about approx. Near to 1000 rupees for 6 Kg front load you may buy it.","votes":"0","username":"Bhavin Patel","date":"2022-09-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why this product not deliverable to my address","answer":"Seller may not have that facility.","votes":"0","username":"Bhavin Patel","date":"2022-09-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Arial pack is different, is it guarenty products?","answer":"Good product","votes":"0","username":"Shivashabkiar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product With scoop","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Jophy V J","date":"2022-03-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Active fragrance","answer":"Yes, mild fragrance is there. This could be find on washed clothes also","votes":"0","username":"Mr. P.K.M","date":"2022-02-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf8f5ed47bf2e548cae7"},"product_asin":"B07DP7779R","QAs":[{"question":"how much pods for a wash of 6 kgs washing will be needed under normal condition?","answer":"1 pod is enough for a normal wash","votes":"0","username":"Deepa","date":"2019-09-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"When we have to drop?","answer":"In the washing machine it self along with the clothes . It is made out of dissolvable casing which melts when it comes in contact with water !","votes":"0","username":"Vanessa","date":"2019-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used for front load machine?","answer":"Yes. It is for the front load machine. However, can be used on top loading as well.","votes":"0","username":"SB-ACP","date":"2019-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"There are only 12 washes??","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"SB-ACP","date":"2019-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use whirlpool outomatic washing machine","answer":"You can use it with any front or top loading automatic machines.","votes":"0","username":"SB-ACP","date":"2019-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many pods are there ?","answer":"12","votes":"0","username":"Rustom Dara Mehta","date":"2019-02-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Two questions please.1) Are there good for coloured clothes 2) are they usable for top load washing machines","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Rustom Dara Mehta","date":"2019-02-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it in semi automatic washing machines?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Rustom Dara Mehta","date":"2019-02-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many pods in box","answer":"12 Pods","votes":"0","username":"Nirjay","date":"2019-01-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"In tablet it having washing powder aa","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Rustom Dara Mehta","date":"2019-02-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf905ed47bf2e548caf7"},"product_asin":"B09R4RWG84","QAs":[{"question":"Is it useful to fully automatic washing machine","answer":"Yes it is useful for washing clothes","votes":"0","username":"Santhosh Goyal","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference between 4 + 2 and 5 + 3 matic","answer":"4+2 = 6 kg. Comes in often 3 packs of 2kg each, it also means buy 4kg and free 2kg total 6kg.","votes":"0","username":"B.Kumar","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the date of expiry ?","answer":"Expires with in 3months","votes":"0","username":"Santhosh Goyal","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between Green and Blue color packs?","answer":"Blue color package is for top load washing machine and green color package is for front load washing machine","votes":"0","username":"TEJA KOONATI","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return policy can applicable or not?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"TEJA KOONATI","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf905ed47bf2e548caff"},"product_asin":"B07BHGWPKV","QAs":[{"question":"Is this use for fully automatic washing mechine?","answer":"NO. THIS IS NORMALLY USED FOR NORMAL WASHING. FOR WASHING MACHINE YOU MUST USE ARIEL MATIC. IT IS ALSO AVAILABLE IN FRONT LOAD AND TOP LOAD VARIANTS.","votes":"0","username":"JOMART","date":"2020-12-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf915ed47bf2e548cb01"},"product_asin":"B09R4SF6QN","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"The packet i got says 2024...","votes":"0","username":"Haider a tangoo","date":"2022-09-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any expiry date?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RK Shrivastava","date":"2022-09-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date","answer":"It doesn't expire","votes":"0","username":"RK Shrivastava","date":"2022-09-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Airel surf sure","answer":"Actually it works","votes":"0","username":"Amrita Jha","date":"2022-09-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use semi automatic and hand wash ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ajimon","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf935ed47bf2e548cb10"},"product_asin":"B06ZZJ7NVH","QAs":[{"question":"mrp is not available on product . How to be sure its original as product in market is available with mrp . Then why there product doesn't have mrp ?","answer":"Bro product price 454 rs. I am using it from last 2 month  it is orginal","votes":"0","username":"Arshdeep  singh‚Ä¶","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it without using washing machine","answer":"Yes you can.","votes":"0","username":"TG","date":"2022-10-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to cancel the order","answer":"I like Airel top load powder and using for past 20 years. Then why shd I cancel the order.","votes":"0","username":"K N Mohan","date":"2022-10-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"On Flipkart box colour is green Why?","answer":"Green  colour box is for front loaded washing machine bro","votes":"0","username":"Arshdeep  singh‚Ä¶","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Its Manufaturing  date","answer":"Super","votes":"0","username":"M.NATARAJAN","date":"2022-09-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expairy date please","answer":"24 month afyer manufacturing","votes":"0","username":"Arshdeep  singh‚Ä¶","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for top load fully automatic washing machine?","answer":"Yes, it is for top load washing machine.","votes":"0","username":"vasant pathak","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's product useful in fully automatic washing machine or not","answer":"Ofcourse it is. I used since two years without problem.","votes":"0","username":"Biswanath p.","date":"2022-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"24 month","votes":"0","username":"Arshdeep  singh‚Ä¶","date":"2022-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is no *Buy Now* Option coming","answer":"Change the pincode and try or wait","votes":"0","username":"Robin Puthussery","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636caf955ed47bf2e548cb28"},"product_asin":"B07BHH32N7","QAs":[{"question":"Can we use in top load washing machine","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Aparna Chakraborty","date":"2021-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"how is Color detergent different from the normal product","answer":"It's same...","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the mrp on the pack?","answer":"280.00","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2020-11-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"how is Ariel color for washing white clothes?","answer":"Good..it doesn't harm ur clothes at all..n removes stains also.","votes":"0","username":"sharfu.t","date":"2019-10-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for front load washing machine","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shom saha","date":"2019-10-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it used for fully automatic","answer":"Yes.....üíê","votes":"0","username":"SUDHIR KUMAR SINGH KUSHWAH","date":"2019-10-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use for topload","answer":"Not yet tried","votes":"0","username":"Vinay Kr. Singhi","date":"2020-03-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are we going to get free 500kg detergent pack with 1.5kg pack","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"mohd malik","date":"2019-07-13 00:00:00"}]}
